[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "HTML stands for 'Hyper Text Markup Language'.",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Python is a statically typed programming language.",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "JavaScript can be used for both front-end and back-end web development.",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "GitHub is a version control system.",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Linux is an open-source operating system.",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "An 'algorithm' is a step-by-step procedure to solve a problem.",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Java is a low-level programming language.",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "SQL is used for programming interactive websites.",
        "answer": false
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "In programming, 'OOP' stands for Object-Oriented Programming.",
        "answer": true
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "An IDE stands for 'Integrated Development Environment'.",
        "answer": true
    }
]
